### Contact

risingsunadvertisingart@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hugolaw (LinkedIn) www.cargocollective.com/hugolaw (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

Graphic Design

Adobe Creative Suite

Illustrator

### Languages

Cantonese (Native or Bilingual)

Mandarin Chinese (Professional Working)

English (Native or Bilingual)

### Honors-Awards

Watsons Health Beauty and Wellness Awards 2014 - Diamond Awards

### Hugo Law

Senior Business Development, Branding, Marketing, and Creative Consultant.

Hong Kong SAR

### Summary

Experienced Senior Business Development Manager / Marketing Manager / Multimedia Creative with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and service industry. Skilled in Data Analytics, Digital Strategy, Typography, Creative Direction and Storyboarding, Adobe Master Suite, Autodesk Maya, Microsoft Office 365. Strong marketing professional with a Bachelor's of Science focused on Mass Communication from Rochester College.

### Experience

M800 Limited

Senior Business Development Manager | Managed Enterprise Solutions (maaiiconnect Platform) at M800 May 2020 - August 2020 (4 months)

Developed new business vertical, managed business partnership programs, worked together with the marketing department's campaigns, and resulted as one of the top 5 participants within the whole company.

### Cherrypicks

Manager - Business Development and Client Services August 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 4 months)

16 - 19/F, 10 Knutsford Terrace, Tsim Sha Tsui, Kowloon, Hong Kong

Helped major financial institutions to establish their online presence from websites to mobile apps development. Provided practical and innovative Fintech solutions to existing and potential clients. Set up and manage strategic relationships with other companies. Developed new services and products such as Design Thinking Workshop.

IGTech365 | Managed IT Services

Marketing Manager

February 2016 - October 2016 (9 months)

2604 Cypress Ridge Blvd #101, Wesley Chapel, FL 33544

Created marketing plans, budgets, and campaigns. Google Analytics, Google AdWords. Managed all Art, Advertising, and Design related material. Worked directly with the General Manager. Created new concept ideas from start to finish. Re-branded the company. Created new marketing campaigns, SEO, UI/ UX Design, Website. Created new motion graphics, animations, and design elements. Managed video production, color grading, audio editing, photo retouching, scriptwriting, etc..

Fleetistics
Marketing Manager
February 2016 - October 2016 (9 months)
2604 Cypress Ridge Blvd #101, Wesley Chapel, FL 33544

Created marketing plans, budgets, and campaigns. Google Analytics, Google AdWords. Managed all Art, Advertising, and Design related material. Worked directly with the General Manager. Created new concept ideas from start to finish. Re-branded the company. Created new marketing campaigns, SEO, UI/UX Design, Website. Created new motion graphics, animations, and design elements. Managed video production, color grading, audio editing, photo retouching, scriptwriting, etc..

Millennium Graphic & Design, Inc.. TV Advertising Creative Specialist February 2015 - May 2015 (4 months) 317 E. Adrian St., Blissfield, MI 49228

Managed all TV advertising and design related material. Worked directly with the General Manager. Created new concept ideas from start to finish. Created new motion graphic animation and elements. Videos editing, color grading, audio editing, photo retouching, scriptwriting, etc..

Long Far Herbal Medicine Mfg (HK) Ltd Creative Director April 2014 - February 2015 (11 months)

14/F, Ever Gain Plaza Tower One, 88 Container Port Road, Kwai Chung, N.T., HK

Re-branded the 16 years old company. Managed all art, design, advertising related material. Worked directly with the General Manager, Account Manager, and Designer. Watched over project balances. Created new concept ideas from start to finish.

Digital Art Laboratories (DALABS)
Creative Director

#### June 2012 - March 2013 (10 months)

Rm. 2603, 26/F Office Tower, Convention Plaza , No.1 Harbour Rd. Hong Kong

Managed all art and design related material. Worked directly with the General Manager, Account Manager, and Designer. Watched over project balances. Created new concept ideas from start to finish.

### Joseph Photo and Video Services Multimedia Designer November 2011 June 2012 (8 months)

November 2011 - June 2012 (8 months)

Floor 2, May Lun Apartments, 23 Shu Kuk Street, North Point, Hong Kong

Created new conceptual motion graphic videos and elements. Edited video for the wedding day. Retouched photo image. Developed new layout designs for photo albums.

## RingSide Creative Motion Graphic/ Audio Recording Internship March 2011 - October 2011 (8 months)

13320 Northend, Ste. 3000 Oak Park, MI 48237

Created promotional motion graphics for potential clients.

Developed animated typography for multiple projects.

Organized music elements for sound design.

Established positive client relationship.

# Macomb Community College Lab Technician - Creative April 2010 - April 2011 (1 year 1 month) 14500 E. 12 Mile Road Warren, MI USA 48088

Assisted students with various course related software.

Helped students develop a stronger sense of design.

### Education

### Rochester College

Bachelor's of Science, Mass Communication · (2009 - 2011)

### Macomb Community College

Associate's of Art, Art for Advertising, Page Layouts, Web Design, General Studies  $\cdot$  (2004 - 2009)

### Rosaryhill School

High School, Business/Commerce, General · (2002 - 2004)

### Buddhist Hung Sean Chau Memorial College

High School, Business/Commerce, General · (1988 - 2002)